A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1947-1951 FA759
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1947
  - North Carolina, 1947; 1947/236
    - North Carolina, 1947 (Box 376, Folder 2540)
  - Ohio, 1947; 1947/238
    Ohio
    - Ohio, 1947 (Box 376, Folder 2540)
  - Pennsylvania, 1947; 1947/241
    Pennsylvania
    - Pennsylvania, 1947 (Box 377, Folder 2541)
  - Phillipines, 1947; 1947/242
    Philippines
    - Philippines, 1947 (Box 377, Folder 2542)
    - Phillipines - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 1947/242.E
      - Philippines, 1947 (Box 377, Folder 2543)
    - Phillipines - Malaria, 1947; 1947/242.I
      - Philippines, 1947 (Box 377, Folder 2543)
    - Phillipines - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 1947/242.R
      - Philippines, 1947 (Box 377, Folder 2543)
      - Philippines - Libraries - Reports, 1947 (Box 377, Folder 2544)
  - Puerto Rico, 1947; 1947/243
    Puerto Rico
    - Puerto Rico, 1947 (Box 377, Folder 2545)
  - Rhode Island, 1947; 1947/244
    Rhode Island
    - Rhode Island, 1947 (Box 377, Folder 2545)
  - South Carolina, 1947; 1947/246
    South Carolina
    - South Carolina, 1947 (Box 377, Folder 2545)
  - Tennessee, 1947; 1947/248
    Tennessee
    - Tennessee, 1947 (Box 377, Folder 2545)
  - Virginia, 1947; 1947/252
    Virginia
    - Virginia, 1947 (Box 377, Folder 2546)
    - Virginia - Medical Sciences, 1947; 1947/252.A
      - Virginia, 1947 (Box 377, Folder 2546)
  - Washington, 1947; 1947/253
    Washington (State)
    - Washington, 1947 (Box 377, Folder 2546)
  - Wisconsin, 1947; 1947/255
    Wisconsin
    - Wisconsin, 1947 (Box 377, Folder 2546)
  - South America, 1947; 1947/300
    South America
    - South America - Administration, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 2547)
    - South America - Administration, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 2548)
    - South America, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 2549)
    - South America - Medical Sciences, 1947; 1947/300.A
      - South America, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 2549)
    - South America - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1947; 1947/300.D
      - South America, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 2549)
    - South America - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 1947/300.E
      - South America, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 2549)
  - Argentina, 1947; 1947/301
    Argentina
    - Argentina, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 2550)
    - Argentina, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 2551)
  - Bolivia, 1947; 1947/303
    Bolivia
    - Bolivia, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 2551)
  - Brazil, 1947; 1947/305
    Brazil
    - Brazil, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 2552)
    - Brazil - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 1947/305.E
      - Brazil, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 2553)
    - Brazil - Malaria, 1947; 1947/305.I
      - Brazil, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 2553)
    - Brazil - Yellow Fever, 1947; 1947/305.O
      - Brazil, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 2553)
    - Brazil - Tuberculosis, 1947; 1947/305.T
      - Brazil, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 2553)
  - Chile, 1947; 1947/309
    Chile
    - Chile, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2554)
    - Chile - Nursing, 1947; 1947/309.C
      - Chile, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2554)
    - Chile - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 1947/309.E
      - Chile, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2554)
  - Colombia, 1947; 02.1947/311
    Colombia
    - Colombia, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2555)
    - Colombia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1947; 1947/311.D
      - Colombia, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2555)
      - Colombia - National University of Colombia - (Agriculture), 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2556)
  - Costa Rica, 1947; 1947/313
    Costa Rica
    - Costa Rica, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2557)
  - Cuba, 1947; 1947/315
    Cuba
    - Cuba, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2557)
  - Ecuador, 1947; 1947/317
    Ecuador
    - Ecuador, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2557)
    - Ecuador - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 1947/317.E
      - Ecuador, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2557)
  - Guatemala, 1947; 1947/319
    Guatemala
    - Guatemala, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2557)
    - Guatemala - Social Sciences, 1947; 1947/319.S
      - Guatemala, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2557)
  - Haiti, 1947; 1947/320
    Haiti
    - Haiti, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2557)
  - Honduras, 1947; 1947/321
    Honduras
    - Honduras, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2557)
    - Honduras - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1947; 1947/321.D
      - Honduras, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2557)
  - Mexico, 1947; 1947/323
    Mexico
    - Mexico - Administration, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2558)
    - Mexico - (A-H), 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2559)
    - Mexico - (I-Z), 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2560)
    - Mexico - Public Health Education, 1947; 1947/323.L
      - Mexico, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2560)
    - Mexico - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 1947/323.R
      - Mexico, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2560)
  - Nicaragua, 1947; 1947/325
    Nicaragua
    - Nicaragua, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2561)
  - Panama, 1947; 1947/327
    Panama
    - Panama, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2561)
    - Panama - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 1947/327.R
      - Panama, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2561)
  - Peru, 1947; 1947/331
    Peru
    - Peru, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2561)
    - Peru - Medical Sciences, 1947; 1947/331.A
      - Peru, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2562)
    - Peru - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Award, 1947; 1947/331.E
      - Peru, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2562)
  - El Salvador, 1947; 1947/333
    El Salvador
    - Salvador, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2562)
  - Dominican Republic, 1947; 1947/335
    Dominican Republic
    - Dominican Republic, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2562)
    - Dominican Republic - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 1947/335.E
      - Dominican Republic, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2562)
  - Uruguay, 1947; 1947/337
    Uruguay
    - Uruguay, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2562)
    - Uruguay - Nursing, 1947; 1947/337.C
      - Uruguay, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2562)
  - Venezuela, 1947; 1947/339
    Venezuela
    - Venezuela, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2563)
    - Venezuela, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2564)
  - Great Britain, 1947; 1947/400
    Great Britain
    - Great Britain, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2565)
  - England, 1947; 1947/401
    England
    - England (A-H), 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2565)
    - England (I-M), 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2566)
    - England (N-O), 1947 (Box 381, Folder 2567)
    - England - (P-U), 1947 (Box 381, Folder 2568)
    - England - (University A-Z), 1947 (Box 381, Folder 2569)
    - England - (W-Z), 1947 (Box 381, Folder 2570)
    - England, 1947 (Box 381, Folder 2571)
    - England - Medical Sciences, 1947; 1947/401.A
      - England, 1947 (Box 381, Folder 2571)
    - England - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1947; 1947/401.D
      - England, 1947 (Box 381, Folder 2571)
    - England - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 1947/401.E
      - England, 1947 (Box 381, Folder 2571)
    - England - Public Health Education, 1947; 1947/401.L
      - England, 1947 (Box 381, Folder 2571)
    - England - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 1947/401.R
      - England, 1947 (Box 381, Folder 2571)
      - England, 1947 (Box 381, Folder 2572)
    - England - Social Sciences, 1947; 1947/401.S
      - England, 1947 (Box 381, Folder 2572)
  - Ireland, 1947; 1947/403
    Ireland
    - Ireland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 1947/403.E
      - Ireland, 1947 (Box 382, Folder 2573)
  - Scotland, 1947; 1947/405
    Scotland
    - Scotland, 1947 (Box 382, Folder 2574)
    - Scotland - Social Sciences, 1947; 1947/405.S
      - Scotland, 1947 (Box 382, Folder 2574)
  - Wales, 1947; 1947/407
    Wales
    - Wales, 1947 (Box 382, Folder 2574)
  - Australia, 1947; 1947/410
    Australia
    - Australia, 1947 (Box 382, Folder 2575)
    - Australia - Medical Sciences, 1947; 1947/410.A
      - Australia, 1947 (Box 382, Folder 2575)
    - Australia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 1947/410.E
      - Australia, 1947 (Box 382, Folder 2575)
  - New Zealand, 1947; 1947/418
    New Zealand
    - New Zealand, 1947 (Box 382, Folder 2576)
    - New Zealand - Medical Sciences, 1947; 1947/418.A
      - New Zealand, 1947 (Box 382, Folder 2576)
    - New Zealand - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 1947/418.E
      - New Zealand, 1947 (Box 382, Folder 2576)
  - Caribbean Region, 1947; 1947/420
    Caribbean Area
    - Caribbean Region - Administration, 1947 (Box 382, Folder 2577)
    - Caribbean Region - Administration, 1947 (Box 382, Folder 2578)
    - Caribbean Region, 1947 (Box 382, Folder 2579)
  - British Guiana, 1947; 1947/423
    Guyana
    - British Guiana, 1947 (Box 382, Folder 2579)
  - Canada, 1947; 1947/427
    Canada
    - Canada - (Administration), 1947 (Box 383, Folder 2580)
    - Canada - (A-Z), 1947 (Box 383, Folder 2581)
    - Canada - (A-Z), 1947 (Box 383, Folder 2582)
    - Canada - (A-Z), 1947 (Box 383, Folder 2583)
    - Canada - (University: A-Z), 1947 (Box 383, Folder 2584)
    - Canada - Medical Sciences, 1947; 1947/427.A
      - Canada - (A-U), 1947 (Box 383, Folder 2585)
      - University of British Columbia, 1947 (Box 383, Folder 2586)
      - Canada - (U-Z), 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2587)
    - Canada - Nursing, 1947; 1947/427.C
      - Canada, 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2588)
    - Canada - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 1947/427.E
      - Canada, 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2588)
    - Canada - Public Health Demonstrations, 1947; 1947/427.J
      - Canada, 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2588)
    - Canada - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 1947/427.R
      - Canada, 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2588)
    - Canada - Social Sciences, 1947; 1947/427.S
      - Canada, 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2588)
  - West Indies, 1947; 1947/431
    West Indies
    - British West Indies, 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2589)
  - Bermuda, 1947; 1947/437
    Bermuda
    - Bermuda, 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2589)
    - Bermuda - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 1947/437.E
      - Bermuda, 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2589)
  - Trinidad, 1947; 1947/451
    Trinidad
    - Trinidad, 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2589)
  - Sri Lanka, 1947; 1947/462
    Sri Lanka
    - Sri Lanka - Nursing, 1947; 1947/462.C
      - Sri Lanka, 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2589)
  - India, 1947; 1947/464
    India
    - India - Administration, 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2590)
    - India - (A-R), 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2591)
    - India - Sankaran, C., 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2592)
    - India - (S-Z), 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2593)
    - India - Medical Sciences, 1947; 1947/464.A
      - India, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2594)
    - India - Nursing, 1947; 1947/464.C
      - India, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2594)
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 1947/464.E
      - India - Government Fellows - (A-Z), 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2595)
      - India - (A-Z), 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2596)
    - India - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 1947/464.R
      - India, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2597)
    - India - Social Sciences, 1947; 1947/464.S
      - India, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2597)
  - Pakistan, 1947; 1947/465
    Pakistan
    - Pakistan - Nursing, 1947; 1947/465.C
      - Pakistan, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2598)
    - Pakistan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 1947/465.E
      - Pakistan, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2598)
  - Burma, 1947; 1947/468
    Myanmar
    - Burma, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2598)
    - Burma - Medical Sciences, 1947; 1947/468.A
      - Burma, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2598)
    - Burma - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 1947/468.R
      - Burma, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2598)
  - Iraq, 1947; 1947/470
    Iraq
    - Iraq, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2598)
  - Malaysia, 1947; 1947/473
    Malaysia
    - Malaysia, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2598)
  - Africa, 1947; 1947/475
    Africa
    - Africa, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2598)
    - Africa - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 1947/475.R
      - Africa, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2598)
  - Ethiopia, 1947; 1947/477
    Ethiopia
    - Ethiopia, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2598)
  - Egypt, 1947; 1947/485
    Egypt
    - Egypt - Administration, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2599)
    - Egypt - (A-Z), 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2600)
  - South Africa, 1947; 1947/487
    South Africa
    - South Africa, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2600)
    - South Africa - Social Sciences, 1947; 1947/487.S
      - South Africa, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2600)
  - France, 1947; 1947/500
    France
    - France - (A-Z), 1947 (Box 386, Folder 2601)
    - France - (A-Z), 1947 (Box 386, Folder 2602)
    - France - (A-Z), 1947 (Box 386, Folder 2603)
    - France - Medical Sciences, 1947; 1947/500.A
      - France, 1947 (Box 386, Folder 2604)
    - France - Nursing, 1947; 1947/500.C
      - France, 1947 (Box 386, Folder 2604)
    - France - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 1947/500.E
      - France, 1947 (Box 386, Folder 2604)
    - France - Declinations, 1947; 1947/500.F
      - France, 1947 (Box 386, Folder 2604)
    - France - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 1947/500.R
      - France, 1947 (Box 386, Folder 2604)
  - Vietnam, 1947; 1947/509
    Vietnam
    - Vietnam, 1947 (Box 386, Folder 2605)
  - Asia, 1947; 1947/600
    Asia
    - Asia, 1947 (Box 386, Folder 2605)
    - Asia - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 1947/600.R
      - Asia, 1947 (Box 386, Folder 2605)
  - China, 1947; 1947/601
    China
    - China - Administration, 1947 (Box 386, Folder 2606)
    - China - (A-Z), 1947 (Box 387, Folder 2607)
    - China - (A-Z), 1947 (Box 387, Folder 2608)
    - China - (A-Z), 1947 (Box 387, Folder 2609)
    - China - Medical Sciences, 1947; 1947/601.A
      - China, 1947 (Box 387, Folder 2610)
    - China - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 1947/601.E
      - China, 1947 (Box 387, Folder 2610)
    - China - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 1947/601.R
      - China, 1947 (Box 387, Folder 2610)
  - Taiwan, 1947; 1947/605
    - Taiwan - Nursing, 1947; 1947/605.C
      - Taiwan, 1947 (Box 387, Folder 2611)
  - Japan, 1947; 1947/609
    Japan
    - Japan - (A-J), 1947 (Box 387, Folder 2611)
    - Japan - (K-Z), 1947 (Box 387, Folder 2612)
    - Japan - Nursing, 1947; 1947/609.C
      - Japan, 1947 (Box 387, Folder 2612)
    - Japan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Award, 1947; 1947/609.E
      - Japan, 1947 (Box 387, Folder 2612)
    - Japan - Social Sciences, 1947; 1947/609.S
      - Japan, 1947 (Box 387, Folder 2612)
      - EVANS-1 Evans, Roger F. "Japan-Korea Diary", 1947 (Box 562, Folder 3832)
        General note
        Stack Material
  - Korea, 1947; 1947/613
    Korea
    - Korea, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2613)
    - Korea - Medical Sciences, 1947; 1947/613.A
      - Korea, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2613)
    - Korea - Nursing, 1947; 1947/613.C
      - Korea, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2613)
    - Korea - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 1947/613.E
      - Korea, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2613)
    - Korea - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 1947/613.R
      - Korea, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2613)
    - Korea - Social Sciences, 1947; 1947/613.S
      - Korea, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2613)
  - Thailand, 1947; 1947/617
    Thailand
    - Thailand - Medical Sciences, 1947; 1947/617.A
      - Thailand, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2613)
  - Holland, 1947; 1947/650
    Netherlands
    - Netherlands - (A-T), 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2614)
    - Netherlands - (U-Z), 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2615)
    - Holland - Medical Sciences, 1947; 1947/650.A
      - Netherlands, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2615)
    - Holland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 1947/650.E
      - Netherlands, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2615)
    - Holland - Health Services, 1947; 1947/650.K
      - Netherlands, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2615)
      - LOG-2 Logan, John A. "Recommendations for the Promotion of Sanitary Engineering in the Netherlands", 1947 (Box 562, Folder 3833)
    - Holland - Public Health Education, 1947; 1947/650.L
      - Netherlands, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2615)
    - Holland - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 1947/650.R
      - Netherlands, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2615)
  - Indonesia, 1947; 1947/655
    Indonesia
    - Indonesia, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2616)
  - Sumatra, 1947; 1947/657
    - Sumatra, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2616)
  - Europe, 1947; 1947/700
    Europe
    - Europe, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2616)
    - LEAV-1 Leavall, Hugh R. "England and Scandinavia Diary", 1947 (Box 562, Folder 3834)
  - Ethiopia, 1947; 1947/701
    - Ethiopia, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2617)
  - Afghanistan, 1947; 1947/703
    Afghanistan
    - Afghanistan, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2617)
  - Austria, 1947; 1947/705
    Austria
    - Austria, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2617)
    - Austria - Medical Sciences, 1947; 1947/705.A
      - Austria, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2617)
    - Austria - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 1947/705.R
      - Austria, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2617)
    - Austria - Social Sciences, 1947; 1947/705.S
      - Austria, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2617)
    - Austria - Tuberculosis, 1947; 1947/705.T
      - Austria, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2617)
  - Belgium, 1947; 1947/707
    Belgium
    - Belgium, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2618)
    - Belgium - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 1947/707.R
      - Belgium, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2618)
    - Belgium - Social Sciences, 1947; 1947/707.S
      - Belgium, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2618)
  - Yugoslavia, 1947; 1947/710
    Serbia; Montenegro
    - Yugoslavia, 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2619)
    - Yugoslavia - Nursing, 1947; 1947/710.C
      - Yugoslavia, 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2619)
    - Yugoslavia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 1947/710.E
      - Yugoslavia, 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2619)
    - Yugoslavia - Public Health Education, 1947; 1947/710.L
      - Yugoslavia, 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2619)
  - Bulgaria, 1947; 1947/711
    Bulgaria
    - Bulgaria, 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2619)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1947; 1947/712
    Czech Republic; Slovakia
    - Czechoslovakia, 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2620)
    - Czechoslovakia, 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2621)
  - Denmark, 1947; 1947/713
    Denmark
    - Denmark, 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2622)
    - Denmark - Medical Sciences, 1947; 1947/713.A
      - Denmark, 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2622)
    - Denmark - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1947; 1947/713.D
      - Denmark, 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2622)
    - Denmark - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 1947/713.E
      - Denmark, 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2622)
    - Denmark - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 1947/713.R
      - Denmark, 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2622)
  - Germany, 1947; 1947/717
    Germany
    - Germany - (A-P), 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2623)
    - Germany - (A-P), 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2624)
    - Germany - Publications, 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2625)
    - Germany - (R-T), 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2626)
    - Germany - (U-Z), 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2627)
    - Germany - Medical Sciences, 1947; 1947/717.A
      - Germany, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2628)
    - Germany - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1947; 1947/717.D
      - Germany, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2628)
    - Germany - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 1947/717.E
      - Germany, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2628)
    - Germany - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 1947/717.R
      - Germany, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2628)
      - Press Personnel (1) - PP, 1947 (Box 563, Folder 3835)
      - Press Personnel (1) - PP, 1947 (Box 563, Folder 3836)
    - Germany - Social Sciences, 1947; 1947/717.S
      - Germany, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2628)
  - Tanzania, 1947; 1947/723
    Tanzania
    - Tanzania, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2629)
  - Greece, 1947; 1947/749
    Greece
    - Greece, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2629)
    - Greece - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1947; 1947/749.D
      - Greece, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2629)
    - Greece - Malaria, 1947; 1947/749.I
      - Greece, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2629)
    - Greece - Social Sciences, 1947; 1947/749.S
      - Greece, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2629)
  - Hungary, 1947; 1947/750
    Hungary
    - Hungary - (A-Z), 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2630)
    - Hungary - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1947; 1947/750.D
      - Hungary, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2631)
    - Hungary - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 1947/750.E
      - Hungary, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2631)
    - Hungary - Malaria, 1947; 1947/750.I
      - Hungary, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2631)
    - Hungary - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 1947/750.R
      - Hungary, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2631)
  - Italy, 1947; 1947/751
    Italy
    - Italy, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2632)
    - Italy - Medical Sciences, 1947; 1947/751.A
      - Italy, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2633)
    - Italy - Nursing, 1947; 1947/751.C
      - Italy, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2633)
    - Italy - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 1947/751.E
      - Italy, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2633)
    - Italy - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 1947/751.R
      - Italy, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2633)
    - Italy - Social Sciences, 1947; 1947/751.S
      - Italy, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2633)
  - Norway, 1947; 1947/767
    Norway
    - Norway, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2634)
    - Norway - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 1947/767.E
      - Norway, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2634)
    - Norway - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 1947/767.R
      - Norway, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2634)
    - Norway - Social Sciences, 1947; 1947/767.S
      - Norway, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2634)
  - Iran, 1947; 1947/771
    Iran
    - Iran, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2635)
    - Iran - Nursing, 1947; 1947/771.C
      - Iran, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2635)
  - Portugal, 1947; 1947/773
    Portugal
    - Portugal, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2635)
    - Portugal - Nursing, 1947; 1947/773.C
      - Portugal, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2635)
  - Romania, 1947; 1947/783
    ROmania
    - Romania, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2635)
  - Ukraine, 1947; 1947/784
    Ukraine
    - Ukraine, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2635)
  - Russia, 1947; 1947/785
    Russia
    - USSR, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2636)
    - Russia - Medical Sciences, 1947; 1947/785.A
      - USSR, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2636)
    - Russia - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 1947/785.R
      - USSR, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2636)
    - Russia - Social Services, 1947; 1947/785.S
      - USSR, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2636)
  - Latvia, 1947; 1947/786
    Latvia
    - Latvia, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2637)
  - Finland, 1947; 1947/787
    Finland
    - Finland, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2637)
    - Finland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 1947/787.E
      - Finland, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2637)
    - Finland - Social Sciences, 1947; 1947/787.S
      - Finland, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2637)
  - Lithuania, 1947; 1947/788
    Lithuania
    - Lithuania, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2637)
  - Poland, 1947; 1947/789
    Poland
    - Poland, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2638)
    - Poland - Medical Sciences, 1947; 1947/789.A
      - Poland, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2639)
    - Poland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 1947/789.E
      - Poland, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2639)
    - Poland - Health Services, 1947; 1947/789.K
      - Poland, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2639)
    - Poland - Public Health Education, 1947; 1947/789.L
      - Poland, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2639)
    - Poland - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 1947/789.R
      - Poland, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2639)
    - Poland - Social Sciences, 1947; 1947/789.S
      - Poland, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2639)
  - Spain, 1947; 1947/795
    Spain
    - Spain (Box 391, Folder 2639)
    - Spain - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 1947/795.R
      - Spain (Box 391, Folder 2639)
  - Sweden, 1947; 1947/800
    Sweden
    - Sweden, 1947 (Box 392, Folder 2640)
    - Sweden - Medical Sciences, 1947; 1947/800.A
      - Sweden, 1947 (Box 392, Folder 2641)
    - Sweden - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 1947/800.E
      - Sweden, 1947 (Box 392, Folder 2641)
    - Sweden - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 1947/800.R
      - Sweden, 1947 (Box 392, Folder 2641)
    - Sweden - Social Sciences, 1947; 1947/800.S
      - Sweden, 1947 (Box 392, Folder 2641)
  - Switzerland, 1947; 1947/803
    Switzerland
    - Switzerland, 1947 (Box 392, Folder 2642)
    - Switzerland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 1947/803.E